

CONTACT



Phone: 0344 4912684



ahmadsohail1819@gmail.com



Address: Kohat, Pakistan

SKILLS

// Professional

Creativity

Teamwork

Communucation

Hardwork

// Technical

Bootstrap 4 & 5

HTML 5, CSS 3

Javascript, JS ES6

React is

Photoshop, XD, Figma to HTML GIT & GITHUB and GITBUCKET

MUHAMMAD SOHAIL

Front - End Developer

Hello, I'm Sohail

Over the past 1 years, as a Front-end Developer, I have designed, developed, and launched customized, highly responsive websites and Web solutions using advanced technologies. In addition, I have consistently met client expectations and project milestones while working effectively in deadline-driven environments. Please consider the following highlights Designed and developed front-end for 180+ webpages using , JavaScript, HTML5, and CSS3 Bootstrap 4 and 5 and some project in React js

EXPERIENCE

TRINING
WEB DEVELOPMENT

Nov 2019 - May 2020

IT ARTIFICER | Peshawer

I have six month trining certificate in web development in which include these skill and tools HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Javascript ES6, Bootstrap 4 / 5, PHP, SQL.

FRONT - END DEVELOPER

Jun 2020 - Dec 2020

IT GURO I Peshawer

I have 7 month experiance in Front - End Development with IT GURO company Peshawer with these skill and tools HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Javascript ES6, Bootstrap 4 / 5, and Basic of React js

EDUCATION

BS - COMPUTER SCIENCE

Oct 2019 - Dic 2022

Virtual University of Lahore

I am now Stusying in BS-Computer from Virtual University Lahore and now active semester Five

DE ARTS

AUT 2017 - SPR 2019

Allama Iqbal Open Unversity (AIOU)

I complete BA degree from Allam Iqbal Open University Islamabad

REFERENCES

HAIDER ALI SEO - Founder IT ARTIFICER, Peshawer IT Park

Phone: +92 333 9296314, Email: info@itartificer.com

ZULFIQAR ALI Web developer IT ARTIFICER, Peshawer IT Park

Phone: +92 308 5548086, Email: zulfiqarali0038@gmail.com